주말에 새로나온
스타워즈 게임 할래?
Hey, want to spend
some time playing the new
Star Wars game
this weekend?
컴퓨터 하는 시간을
좀 줄이려고 했는데
Oh, I don't know.
I kind of promised myself
I'd get off the computer,
be more physically active.
운동을 해야겠어
Get some exercise...
지금도 3층까지
걸어 올라가잖아
You're about to walk up
three flights of stairs.
그러네,
그럼 게임 하자
Good point, I'm in.
이러면 재밌겠다
KOOTHRAPPALI:
You know what would be great?
예전처럼 하는거야
Let's do it
like the old days.
게임 마라톤?
You mean, are you talking
gaming marathon?
토요일 아침부터 48시간
Yeah. Start Saturday morning,
go 48 hours,
침낭에 야식에
sleeping bags,
junk food...
엄마가 연락 못 하게
폰도 꺼두고
Turn off our phones
so our moms can't call.
몇 년 전
워크래프트 파티처럼
It would be like our World Of
Warcraft a few years ago
그때 옆집에서 신고했잖아
when the neighbors
called the cops on us.
(both chuckle)
냄새 때문에 신고당했지
They called the cops
because of the smell.
우리가 죽은 줄 알고
They thought we were dead.
그땐 잘 나갔었지
We were badass back in the day.
콜
All right, let's do it.
48시간 스타워즈 마라톤
48 hours of Star Wars gaming.
기다려라, 알데란
It's on like Alderaan.
(all laugh)
쉘든
Hey, Sheldon,
주말에 시간 비워둬
clear your weekend.
Starting Saturday morning,
스타워즈 마라톤 할거야
Star Wars marathon
Whoohoo!
영화 아니면 게임?
Movies or video games?
보드게임?
No, board game?
카드 놀이?
Or trading card games?
레고? 변장?
Or Lego's? Or dress up?
만화책?
Or comic books?!
스타워즈 소설 낭독회?
Or dramatic readings
of novelizations?!
뭐든 좋아
Yes to all!
온라인 게임을 할 계획이야
We are going to play
the online game.
온라인 게임?
The online game?!
앗싸!
Bully!
은하간 판타지도
재밌긴 하겠지만
Gentlemen, as much as I'm sure
Sheldon would enjoy
playing intergalactic
make-believe,
우리는 다른 일정이 있어
he and I have other plans.
이모의 93번째 생신을
축하하러 갈거야
We are attending my Aunt Flora's
93rd birthday party.
난 못 간다고 해줘
Just tell her I can't come.
우리가 빠지면 실망하실걸
She'll be disappointed
if we don't show up.
93살이잖아
She's 93.
실망해도 오래 안 가
She won't be disappointed
for very long.
연애 계약서에 나온
사항을 모두 지켰다고
No, hang on.
I followed all the protocols
set forth by you in the
relationship agreement.
72시간 전에
서면 요청을 제출했고
I made a written record request
72 hours in advance.
타이어 공기압도 확인했어
I checked the tire pressure
on the car.
질병통제센터에 연락해
I even contacted the Centers
For Disease Control to find out
OC에 가려면 어떤 주사를
맞아야 하는지 물어봤어
what shots they recommend
for travel to Orange County.
그냥 가도 된대
FYI, it's none.
계약서는 네가 원하는대로
하도록 만들어진게 아냐
Amy, the relationship
agreement was not designed
for either one of us
to get our way.
넌 그럴 때 써먹잖아
You use it to get your way.
올바르게 사용하는 거지
I use it to
get the right way.
원하는대로 일이
풀리는 건 우연일 뿐
The fact that
the right way is
also my way is
a happy coincidence.
약속했잖아
You gave me your word.
나랑 가야해
You're coming with me.
보고 싶을거야, 쉘든
We'll miss you, Sheldon.
Yeah, well,
판타지 속 행성에서
몬스터를 물리치며
who wants to spend the whole
weekend, running around
주말을 낭비하고
싶지 않아
a bunch of pretend planets
battling made up monsters.
그건 애들이나 하는거라고
That's for babies.
광선검도 있잖아
Yeah, but it's got lightsabers.
에이미, 제발,
광선검도 있대
Yeah, please, Amy!
It's got lightsabers!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
DC 기타 미국드라마 갤러리
The Big Bang Theory 5x19
The Weekend Vortex
Original Air Date on March 8, 2012
자막 공대언니
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
- Hello Stuart.
- Hey Sheldon.
안녕
뭐 찾는 거 있어?
Help you with anything?
어떤 여성 분의 93번째
생일 파티에 가게 됐어
Yes. I'm attending a party this
weekend, for a 93-year-old woman.
선물 좀 추천해줘
Can you recommend a gift?
어렵군
Uh, I don't know.
엑스칼리버에 테니스 공을
꽂으면 지팡이로 써도 되겠다
Could put a tennis ball
on the end of Excalibur.
Make a pretty badass cane.
- 테니스 공도 제공하는 거야?
- 아니
Do you supply the the tennis balls?
No.
그럼 됐어
Then no.
다른 건 없어?
What else?
Hmm...
한정판 배트맨
유틸리티 벨트가 있어
Oh, have this collectors edition
Batman utility belt.
휴대용 약통으로
활용할 수 있겠네
Maybe she can use it as a
wearable pill caddy.
코스튬 없이 벨트만
차면 바보 같을걸
Well, she'd just look silly
wearing that
without the rest of the costume.
미안, 우리 가게에는
이런 것 밖에 없어
I'm sorry Sheldon, that's it.
That's all I got.
아냐, 괜찮아
Oh, it's not your fault.
열차모형 가게에 들리고
I've been to the
model train store.
전자제품 가게에도 갔었어
I've been to Radio Shack.
이 여자한테는 대체
뭘 선물해야 하지
This woman is
impossible to shop for.
쉘든이 여자 문제로
고민하다니
I'd make fun of Sheldon
for having girl problems
너무 충격 먹어서
놀리지도 못하겠네
if I wasn't in shock that
Sheldon has girl problems.
아냐, 맘껏 놀려
No, Leonard,
go ahead and mock.
아빠가 늘 그랬어
Like my daddy always said,
"Shelly, women aren't anything
여자는 골치덩어리라고
but flippin' pains
in the bottom."
아빠가 그렇게 말했어?
That's what your
father used to say?
욕이랑 '히허' 소리는 뺐지만
Well, I took out the
bad words and the yeehaw,
무슨 말인지 알지?
but you get the gist.
파티에 가고 싶지 않으면
Look, if you don't want to go
그냥 가지 마
to the party, just don't go.
넌 성인이잖아
You're a grown man.
어른답게 행동해
Act like one.
친구들이랑 게임하며
주말을 보내고 싶다고 말해
Tell Amy you want to spend
the weekend having a sleepover
and playing video games
with your friends.
의외로 좋아할 수도 있어
Maybe she'll dig it.
여자들은 확 쥐어잡는
스타일을 좋아해
Women like a firm hand
on the tiller.
난 어딜 잡아야 할지
모르겠더라
I can never find the tiller.
책도 읽었는데
도움이 안 됐어
I got a book; it didn't help.
내가 누군가의
노예가 된다면
Yeah, I always thought
if I were ever enslaved,
다른 행성에서 온
진보된 종일거라 생각했어
it would be by an advanced
species from another planet,
글레데일 출신
흔녀가 아니라
not some hotsy-totsy
from Glendale.
이런 상황에서
도움이 될 앱을 받았어
Now, I downloaded an app that
might be helpful
in this situation.
(whip cracks)
(all laugh)
네 말이 맞아
You're right.
채찍 소리처럼 날카로운
두뇌로 해결해야겠어
I'm smart as a whip. I should
be able to figure this out.
이번 주말에
애들이랑 놀기로 했는데
Hey, listen,
I kind of made plans
with the guys this weekend,
but then I wondered,
우리 사이가 아직
베타 테스트 중이라
because we're in this
relationship-beta-test,
허락받아야 하는지
잠깐 고민했어
if I should have
asked you first.
하지만 너한테 먼저 물어보면
Then I thought
if I did check with you first,
너무 진지하다고
생각할까봐 걱정했는데
then you'd think that I was
taking things too seriously.
그러다 코피가 터졌어
And then-en I got a nosebleed.
물어볼 필요 없어
You don't have to check with me.
맘대로 해
Do whatever you want.
Oh.
다른 반응을 기대했는데
I guess I was hoping for a
different reaction, but okay.
뭘 기대했길래?
Really, what were
you hoping for?
글쎄
I don't know,
네가 조금 서운해하다가
깨닫게 될 줄 알았어
maybe that you'd
be a little upset,
and then you'd realize that
나는 통제할 수 없는
야생마라는 걸
I'm a stallion
that has to run free.
그리고 나에게
더욱 매력을 느끼겠지
And that would
turn you on a little.
난 연기자야,
다시 물어봐
Okay, I'm an actress.
Ask me again.
주말에 애들이랑
게임해도 될까?
Do you mind
if I spend the weekend
playing video games
with the guys?
주말 내내?
Wha... the entire weekend?
그럼 한번도 못 보는 거야?
You mean I wouldn't
see you at all?
But I j...
아니지
No, no...
이런 건 예상했어
I knew what I was getting into.
레너드는 길들여지지 않아
You can't put a saddle
on Leonard Hofstadter.
여기 좀 덥지 않아?
Oh, my, is it getting hot
in here?
Ay,papi.
Ay papi?
¿Ay papi?
그건 뭐야?
(chuckles)
What is that?
연기 컨셉이지
- An acting choice.
- Oh.
넌 흥분되면
스피디 곤잘레스가 되는 거야?
So you chose that when
you become turned on,
you turn into Speedy Gonzalez?
문제 있어, 파피?
Choo got a problem
with that, papi?
Uh-uh.
페니! 페니! 페니!
(knocking)
SHELDON: Penny! Penny! Penny!
미안해, 야생마
Sorry, Stallion.
네 기린 친구가 왔네
Your weird friend
Giraffe is here.
Hello, Penny!
선물을 전해주러 들렸어
I just stopped by to
bring you this gift.
꼬마곰?
고마워
Gummy bears?
Thank you.
이젠 나한테 빚진 게 있으니
Now that you're
in my debt...
에이미 좀 설득해줘
...please manipulate Amy
into releasing me from my
같이 파티에 참석하지
않아도 되게 도와줘
commitment to attend her
aunt's tedious birthday party.
꿈 깨
Not a chance.
All right.
젤리로 어림도
없을 거 같아서
I thought the candy
might not be enough
더 센걸 준비했어
so let me up the ante.
(clears throat)
이건 쿠퍼 쿠폰이야
These are Cooper Coupons.
내가 널 위해
할 수 있는 일들이지
These are for various things
I can do for you.
이건 무료 문법 교정 1회
Um, oh, this one
is for one free grammar check.
Uh...
이메일, 편지, 문신 등에
사용하면 되지
You could use it for emails,
letters,
tattoos, what have you.
Um...
이건 재밌어
Oh, this is fun one!
캘리포니아 과학센터에
견학가는 거야
This is an afternoon with me at
the California Science Center,
잘못된 정보를
지적해줄게
where I point out
their mistakes.
쿠폰 기한에 주의해
Keep an eye on
those expiration dates,
난 여러 번 데였어
I've been burned
more than once.
너네 사이에
끼어들고 싶지 않아
All right, sweetie,
I'm not going to get involved
in your relationship.
쉬운 부탁이잖아
Oh, come on.
It's just a simple favor.
내가 언제 이런
부탁한 적 있어?
Now, when's the last time
I asked you
to do something for me?
어제 귓속에 무당벌레가
있는지 봐달라며
Yesterday. You made me
look in your ear
to see if there was
a ladybug in it.
긴급상황이 아닌
부탁을 한 적 있어?
When is the last time
I asked you to do something
that wasn't a medical emergency?
어제 귓속에 무당벌레가
있는지 봐달라며
Yesterday. You made me
look in your ear
to see if there was
a ladybug in it.
어쩔 수 없네
All right, then,
I have no choice
플랜 B 실행이다
but to go on to plan B.
그건 뭔데?
What's that?
머리가 젖은 채로
I'm going to run around outside
감기가 걸릴 수 있게
돌아다닐 거야
with a wet head and
try to catch a cold.
Good morning.
Hello.
오늘 정말 재밌을 거야
I think you're really
going to enjoy yourself today.
내 친척을 만날 수도 있고
Not only do you get
to meet my relatives,
이모네 양로원이
음식 준비를 맡아서
but since you aunt's nursing
home is catering the party,
모든게 부드러울 거야
all of the food
is incredibly soft.
치아가 쉴 수 있어
It's like a vacation
for your teeth.
그래
All right.
정말 괜찮아?
You sure you're
okay with this?
응
Yes.
이왕 가는거
즐기기로 했어
I decided to find
a way that I could
have this experience
and enjoy it.
노력해줘서 고마워
Thank you. That
means a lot to me.
고맙다니
Oh, don't thank me.
무선기술에 감사해야지
Thank wireless technology.
너네 이모의 지루한
파티에 있으면서도
I realized, I can go
to your aunt's awful party
하루종일 친구들이랑
게임을 할 수 있어
and still spend the whole day
gaming with my friends.
쉘든, 친척들이 너랑
말해보고 싶을텐데
Sheldon, my relatives are going
to want to talk to you,
앉아서 게임이나 하겠다고?
and you're going to be sitting
there playing a game?
좀 무례하지 않아?
Isn't that a
little rude?
문제 없어
Oh, I got that covered.
헤드폰을 낄 거야
Headset.
늙은이들이 하는 말은
하나도 못 들어
I won't hear a word
the old geezers are saying.
나와 약속을
지키는 것보다
You know, if playing that game
is more important to you
게임이 그렇게
중요하다면
than honoring your
commitment to me,
그리고 남자친구를
데리고 간다고 말했지만
and you don't mind me showing up
at a party all by myself
after I've already told
everybody
내가 혼자 가도
개의치 않는다면
I'll be bringing somebody,
then, fine.
집에 가서 게임이나 해
Go home and play your game.
(engine starts)
고마워
Thanks.
있지
Ooh, listen,
케익 한 조각 정도는
갖다주면 좋겠어
I wouldn't mind
a piece of birthday cake,
할머니가 초를 끌 때
침이 안 튀긴다면
provided the old gal's
candle blow is clean and dry.
Here you go.
I've got everything
we'll need for the big game:
마라톤 준비가 다 됐다
lowfat turkey jerky...
저지방 칠면조 육포
low-carb beer...
라이트 맥주
100-calorie snack pack...
100 칼로리 간식
You pick up a Y chromosome
while you were there?
Y 염색체은 안 챙겼어?
You might be short one.
너한테 딱이거든
Hey, I plan on leveling up
in the game,
레벨업은 게임에서 할거야
not my swimsuit size,
thank you very much.
수영복 사이즈가 아니라
Gentlemen, the game
offers us a choice,
여러분, 선택권이 있어
between playing for the Republic
and the light side,
공화국을 위해
싸울 것인가
or the Sith Empire
and the dark side.
아니면 시스제국
편을 들까
Well, we're always
the good guys.
우린 항상 착한 역이잖아
In D&D, we're lawful good,
D&D에서는 lawful good
in City Of Heroes,
we're the heroes,
City Of Heroes에서는 히어로
and Grand Theft Auto,
we pay the prostitutes promptly,
GTA에서는 창녀한테
비용 지불을 하고
and never hit them with a bat.
절대 폭력을 휘두르지 않지
Those women are prostitutes?
걔내들 창녀였어?
You said they were raising money
for stem cell research.
줄기세포 연구에
모금활동 중이라며
Hey, guys, I got a surprise.
할 말이 있어
Uh, if it's yogurt
that helps ladies poop,
쾌변 요구르트라면
라지가 이미 사왔어
I think Raj beat you to it.
No. Bernadette's
going to be playing with us.
베르나데트도 같이 놀거야
So, that's pretty cool, huh?
Right? Sure it is, yeah.
재밌겠지?
물론 그렇지
What, you invited
your girlfriend?!
여자친구를 초대했어?
This is supposed
to be our weekend!
우리끼리만
보내는 시간이잖아
I had no choice.
Last night, she said,
어쩔 수 없었어
"Why don't we go out
for brunch tomorrow
내일 브런치
먹으러 갔다가
and then maybe the Arboretum."
And I said, "Well, no,
수목원에 가면
어떠냐고 해서
"I promised the guys
I was going to play
주말 내내 애들이랑
게임하기로 했다고 말했어
a video game with them
all weekend."
And she said, "That sounds
like fun. Can I come, too?"
그랬더니 같이 놀아도
되냐고 물어보잖아
And then I didn't answer
for a second, and then she said,
잠깐 머뭇거렸더니
"Well, do you not
want me to come?"
자기가 끼는게
싫은지 물어보더군
And then I bought her
a new laptop and the game,
그래서 노트북이랑
게임을 사줬어
and she's parking
the car right now.
지금 주차하고 있어
Is the whip sound app
채찍 소리를
지금 재생하면 맞나?
contextually
appropriate here?
Uh, it is, but I think
you might've waited too long
타이밍이 지나서
이제는 재미없어
for it to be funny.
(whip cracks)
(laughter)
(laughing):
I was wrong; it's still funny.
아직 재밌네
Oh, good.
좋아
(high-pitched laugh)
Oh.
Amy, what's wrong?
에이미, 무슨 일이야?
My boyfriend's a jerk.
내 남자친구는 나쁜 놈이야
Well, I know he didn't
cheat on you,
바람 핀 건 아니잖아
so what happened?
무슨 짓을 했길래?
I had to go to my aunt's
party all by myself,
파티에 혼자 가야했어
and everybody was like,
모두들 이렇게 물어봤지
"Where's this boyfriend
you're always talking about?
남자친구는 어디 갔니?
"Is he real, or did you
make him up like Armen,
아르멘이라는 애완말
사육사처럼 지어낸거 아냐?
the miniature horse breeder?"
Who's Armen the
miniature horse breeder?
애완말 사육사 아르멘은 누구야?
The pretend boyfriend I invented
to get my family off my back.
가족이 너무 닥달해서
꾸며낸 남자친구야
It unraveled quickly when
I couldn't answer the question
질문에 답을 못해서
금방 들통났어
"How'd you two meet?"
'너네는 어떻게 만났니?'
I would have thought
at a miniature horse show.
애완말 축제에서
만났을 줄 알았는데
- Oh, that's good.
- Mm.
그거 좋네
I panicked and said Woodstock.
난 당황해서
우드스탁이라고 말했어
(sighs)
I just wanted to show Sheldon
off to my family.
쉘든을 자랑하고 싶었는데
Sure, I get that.
그렇겠다
I mean, he's your first
boyfriend and all.
처음으로 사귀는
남자친구잖아
Not just my first boyfriend,
he's the best boyfriend.
처음이기도 하지만
최고의 남친이야
I mean, think about it.
생각해봐
I'm dating Sheldon Cooper.
난 쉘든 쿠퍼와
연애 중이야
Yes.
응
On purpose.
고의로 그러고 있지
He's handsome, he's lanky,
잘생기고 키도 크고
he's brilliant,
똑똑하잖아
and his skin has that pale,
waxy quality.
피부는 창백하고 왁스 같아
Well, sickly is the new sexy.
요즘에는 그게 섹시하지
- Yeah.
- Mm.
You know, Amy,
sometimes when you're in
a relationship with someone
진심으로 좋아하는
사람이랑 연애를 하면
you really care about,
the sucky part is,
it leaves you open
to getting hurt.
상처받을 수도 있는 거야
Do you ever worry about
Leonard doing that to you?
레너드한테 상처 받을까봐
걱정되지 않아?
(laughs)
That's hilarious. No.
그럴 리가
Get that guy!
저 놈 잡아
Pew! Pew! Pew! Pew!
Dr. Rostenkowski,
로스텐코우스키 박사
it may interest
you to know
키보드를 누르는 게
'퓨 퓨 퓨'보다 효과적이야
that saying "pew, pew, pew"
isn't as effective
as pressing your
blaster key.
In the same way
that saying "whee!"
랜드스피더를
작동할 때도 마찬가지고
doesn't make the
land speeder go.
Pew!
Raj, Imperial Troopers
on your tail.
라지, 제국의 공격이야
(groaning): Got him.
막았어
When Gandhi advocated his
philosophy of non-violence,
간디가 평화 사상을 펼칠 때
I bet he didn't know how much
fun it was killing stuff.
폭력이 얼마나
재밌는지 몰랐을 거야
All right, I think
we got them all.
다 죽였다
Let's divide up the loot.
물건을 나누자
BERNADETTE: Ooh, look at this
pretty purple robe I just got.
이 보라색 가운 너무 이쁘다
You should put on yours
and then we'll match.
너도 같이 입자
But I worked hard
to get this armor.
난 갑옷을 얻으려고
엄청 노력했는데
Sorry, I just thought
it'd be nice
커풀룩하면
좋을 줄 알았지
if people knew
we were a couple.
Fine, I'll change.
알았어,
갈아입을게
(whip cracks)
(high-pitched laugh)
I don't think I want
to play a game.
게임은 하고 싶지 않아
Oh, come on!
They're playing one
across the hall--
앞집에서 게임 하잖아
we should, too.
우리도 놀자
Okay, we are gonna take
turns bouncing a quarter
테이블에 동전을 튕기고
off the table, and if it
goes into this cup,
컵에 들어가면
the other person
has to drink.
상대방이 마시는 거야
Then you get to
go again...
그럼 다시 한번
던질 기회가 있고
(coin clinks in glass)
Like that?
이렇게?
Wow. Yeah, b-beginner's luck.
응, 운이 좋네
So, now I will drink this entire
cup of beer, and you
이번 판은 내가 마시고
will go again...
(coin clinks in glass)
또 네 차례야
Uh...
All right. So, yeah, okay,
now I'm gonna
한 잔을 마시고
drink this entire cup and then
I'm going to drink another one.
또 한 잔 마셔야겠네
(coin clinks in glass) Okay,
seriously, stop. What the hell?
그만해
Spent a lot of my childhood
어릴 때 자주 했어
throwing coins into wishing
wells hoping for friends.
친구를 사귀려고 우물에
동전을 던지고 빌었지
At a certain point, you
start doing trick shots
재미가 없을 때는
변화구도 던졌어
just to keep
things interesting.
Whoa, give me a second
to catch up here. Hold on.
다 마시게 좀 기다려
(guys cheering
across the hall)
That'd be
my boyfriend
내 남자친구네
happier playing
날 버려두고
his dopey Star Trek game
with his friends
친구들이랑
스타트렉이나 하고
than hanging out with me.
- Wars.
- What?
- 워즈
- 뭐라고?
Star Wars.
스타워즈
They get all cranky
when you mix the two up.
구분하지 않으면 싫어해
What's the difference?
무슨 차인데?
There's absolutely
no difference.
그게 그거지
How do I get him
to treat me better?
나한테 잘해주게
하려면 어떡하지?
All right.
그래
Let me give you
a little girlfriend 101.
내가 팁 좀 줄게
Usually the first move
out of the gate
제일 좋은 방법은
섹스로 굶기는 건데
is you withhold sex,
but that will work better
after Sheldon hits puberty.
이건 사춘기 후에
효과적이야
So, I'd say...
그렇다면
give him the silent treatment.
그냥 무시해
No, he loves that.
Hmm.
아냐, 쉘든은 그걸 좋아해
Our record for sitting
in a room together
서로에게 말을 안 하고
6시간 넘게 있었는데
and not speaking to each other
is six-and-a half hours.
He said it was
a magical evening.
환상적이였다고 하더라
All right, then we're
gonna have to go
그렇다면 좀 오래됐지만
괜찮은 방법이 있어
with an oldie but goodie;
making a scene.
소란 피우기
I don't think I'd
be good at that.
난 그런거 못해
That's why you're
lucky to have me.
내가 도와주면 되지
Back in Omaha, there are
two different restaurants
오마하에서는 내가
출입금지된 식당이 2개야
I'm not allowed into.
Both Chili's.
Bernadette, remember,
your character's
베르나데트,
네 캐릭터는 힐러야
the healer in our group.
You're in charge of healing
all of us, not just Howard.
하워드 뿐만 아니라
모두를 치료해줘
I can't help it.
어쩔 수 없어
My Howie Wowie
has an owie.
하위가 아야 하잖아
That is the most sickeningly
sweet thing
징그럽게 달콤하네
I have ever experienced.
And I am sipping Kool-Aid
through a Red Vine.
캔디로 쿨에이드를
마시는 것보다 훨씬
Sheldon Cooper, I've got
a bone to pick with you,
쉘든 쿠퍼,
따질 게 있어
and I'm about to do it
in front of all your friends.
네 친구들 앞에서 할게
Yeah, you pick that bone.
You pick that bone clean!
그래, 확실하게 따져
I'm gonna publicly shame you,
공개적으로 망신 줄거야
and then sit back as societal
pressure compels you
사회적 압박에 못 이겨
뉘우치는 동안 지켜볼 거야
to modify your behavior.
Ooh, buuurn!
And if you don't start
treating me better,
나한테 잘해주지 않으면
I'm leaving you
사육사 아르멘을
선택하겠어
for a miniature horse breeder
named Armen.
Armen who?
아르멘 성이 뭔데?
Armen... damn it.
아르멘... 젠장
Look, Sheldon, she wanted
to show you off to her family,
에이미는 가족한테
널 자랑하고 싶었는데
and you stood her up, okay?
바람을 맞았어
Look at this adorable,
smushy face.
이 귀엽고 말랑한 얼굴을 봐
Smush, smush, smush.
You're hurting me.
아파
No, Sheldon hurt you.
아니, 쉘든 때문이지
Before; now it's you.
지금은 너 때문이야
Oh.
I think I understand.
이해가 되는 것 같아
You're the one person
내가 남친이라고 말할 수
있는 건 네 특권이야
who can say Sheldon Cooper
is your boyfriend,
but that rings hollow
if you can't lord him
사람들 앞에서 드러내지
못한다면 의미가 없지
over others in the flesh.
I forget what
I bring
내 존재가 파티에
얼마나 중요한지 잊었어
to the party
and what I take away
when I leave.
Please accept these valuable
Cooper Coupons...
보상하는 의미로
쿠퍼 쿠폰을 받아줘
...as restitution.
Sheldon, she doesn't
want your stupid...
쉘든, 그런 쓸모 없는...
Ooh, Science Center.
Redeeming.
과학센터라,
맘에 든다
Let's go.
가자
Well played, Amy Farrah Fowler.
좋은 선택이야, 에이미
Let me get my coat.
겉옷 좀 챙길게
(whip cracks)
Oh, grow up, Leonard.
레너드, 그만해
But e-excuse me,
저기
I have something to say.
난 할 말이 있어
None of you may realize it,
but I was very much
너네는 모르겠지만
looking forward to this weekend.
난 이번 주말을
정말 기대했어
It was gonna be like
예전처럼 넷이서
신나게 놀 계획이었어
the old days-- the four of us
hanging out
playing video games
before you guys
너네가 모두 여자친구가
생기기 전에 말이야
all got girlfriends.
Do you have any idea
what it's like
혼자 솔로인게
얼마나 외로운지 알아?
to be the only one
without a girlfriend?
Even if I get one someday,
언젠가 생기더라도
I'll still be the guy
who got a girl
쉘든 쿠퍼보다
느린 놈이 되잖아
after Sheldon Cooper!
And that's how
a girl makes a scene.
소란은 저렇게 피우는 거야
I'm sorry, sweetie.
미안해, 라지
You're right.
You deserve your weekend.
재밌는 주말 보내
Come on, Amy,
let's go.
가자, 에이미
What about the
Science Center?
과학센터는?
I'll let you hold my hair
while I throw up.
내가 토하는 동안
머리 잡아도 돼
Rain check.
다음 기회에
I'm gonna go, too.
나도 갈래
- I'll miss you.
- 보고 싶을 거야
- 나도
- I'll miss you more.
- No, I'll...
- 내가 더
- 아니, 내가...
Just leave!
그냥 가라고
(sighs)
Okay, now.
됐다
This is the way
it's supposed to be.
이제 할맛이 나네
Men together,
fighting the forces of evil.
남자들끼리 뭉쳐서
악을 물리치는 거야
LEONARD, SHELDON, WOLOWITZ:
Hear! Hear!
옳소
(sighs)
I can't believe
this is only 64 calories.
64kcal 뿐이라니
(pounding at door)
하워드 조엘 왈로위츠
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard Joel Wolowitz!
이틀 동안 걱정했다고
I've been worried sick
for two days,
일부러 폰 꺼놨지
and I know you turned
off your phone!
지금 당장 문 열어
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
You open up this door right now
더 이상 못 참아
because I've had it
up to here!
시체 안치소랑
병원에 갔다가
I have been to the morgue
and the hospital,
망할 계단을 오르느라
30분이나 걸렸어
and I spent the last
half hour
walking up these
ferkakta stairs!
엄마가 데리러 왔네,
가야겠다
That's my ride; got to go.
(whip cracks)
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com
== sync, corrected by elderman ==